Liron Almog

LironAlmog95@gmail.com | 050-5880688 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/lironalmog | https://github.com/Liron-Almog

Self-motivated, fast-learner, autodidact, goal-oriented developer. Detail oriented individual with can-do approach and passion for technology and innovation. Adept at collaborating and great team player with confident leadership and great communication skills. Quick and creative solution finding abilities.

♣ Projects

Grocery Shopping, Mobile App using React Native, NodelS & Express, AWS, MySQL

Cheaper is a grocery shopping app that assists customers in reducing the total cost of their shopping cart. By leveraging NLP (Natural Language Processing), the app recommends the most affordable products during the cart creation process, ensuring the best possible outcome in terms of price optimization.

Circle the Cat, Game using C++ & SFML

Circle the Cat is a puzzle game. The game is based on Breadth-First Search (BFS) algorithm. This game is designed using the principles of object-oriented programming and incorporates design patterns.

Ecommerce, Web using React, Spring and TMDB API

It allows customers to browse movies, add items to cart, and complete purchases. The React front-end offers a seamless user experience with search, cart management, and secure checkout. The Spring back-end handles cart management and purchase recording via a REST API, storing customer information securely in a SQL Server database.

Education

Computer Science, B.Sc.

2019 - present

B.Sc. in computer science at Hadassah Academic College, with high grades.

Work Experience

Private Tutor 2022 - present

Gives private lessons to students in the courses "Introductions to Computer Science" and "Modular Programming", while emphasizing a deep understanding of data structures.

Security Guard & Shift Manager, Government Ministry Justice

2018 - present

military Service

Commander & Fighter, Israel Defense Force

2014 - 2017

I was a fighter solider in the army. Later, I was promoted to be a commander of a large group of soldiers and officers. As part of my role, I had to make complicated and important decisions and also solve problems under pressure.

P Skills

Language

C/C++ | Java | JavaScript | NodeJS |

CSS | HTML | MySQL | React | OS |

OOP & SOLID principle | GitHub |

REST API | Angular

Hebrew - Native

English - High Level